pitchmagic.com 2019-06-05

# PitchMagic Privacy Policy

## Information About All PitchMagic™ Visitors

In general, our website automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to PitchMagic™. We only use such data in the aggregate. This aggregate data helps us determine how much our clients use parts of the website, so we can improve our website to assure that it is as effective as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, PitchMagic™ may use a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our website are visited, and by how many people. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through these cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your email address is.

## Information About You

If you are a PitchMagic™ client, when you access PitchMagic™ you may obtain access to features of the PitchMagic™ online service that contain personal information. Additionally, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service, or when you order a product. We will need certain information -- such as name, Internet address, billing address, credit card number -- in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested.

## Disclosure

PitchMagic™ will only share your information with third parties in accordance with your instructions or as necessary to provide you with a specific service or otherwise in accordance with applicable privacy legislation. As a general rule, we do not and will not sell, rent, share or disclose your personal information without first receiving your permission or as permitted in this Privacy Policy.

## How can I access and change my information?

To view, edit or delete the Personal Information you submitted, email support@pitchmagic.com.

## How is my information protected? 

Whenever Personal Information about you is stored on our computers, that information is password-protected from unauthorized access or use. In addition, this information is kept on servers that are located behind a firewall.

Since your financial information is especially sensitive, we take special care to keep it secure. Your credit card number and financial information are stored on secure, designated servers and access is limited to individuals in departments charged with using such information only in connection with processing your orders for products and services purchased.

Of course, we appreciate your help in safeguarding the integrity of your own and others' privacy. We hope you'll use common sense whenever you disclose Personal Information over the Internet. Just as importantly, we encourage you to let us know immediately if you suspect that the information you share with us is being used in any way contrary to this Privacy Policy. Finally, unfortunately no data transmission over the Internet or the storage of information on servers can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and while we strive to protect your personal information (as described herein), we cannot guarantee or warrant its complete security. To contact us, please send an email to support@pitchmagic.com.

## Privacy Policy Changes

If we elect to change our privacy policy for PitchMagic™, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information andunder what conditions your information may be disclosed.
